foreign
[Music]
I haven't done a YouTube in a while so
我已经有一段时间没有做 YouTube 了，所以是时候
uh
it's time to do one
做一个了，
as you can see
你可以看到
Christmas Is Here
圣诞节来了，
well it's not here yet but
虽然还没到，但
it is coming soon and I am just packing
很快就要到了，我正在
up I've got
收拾东西，我有
some camera equipment here
一些相机 设备在这里
I've got shares I've got water I've got
我有股份我有水我有
coffee I've got clothes I got sleeping
咖啡我有衣服我有睡袋
bag
I'm gonna be heading out real soon to
我很快就要出发去
hit a ferry
搭渡轮到达
make it over to the mainland Vancouver
温哥华大陆
and take some photos of
并拍一些照片 猫头鹰
owls
so
所以
without any further ado
没有任何进一步的
time to pack up the Jeep
时间收拾吉普车，
and uh rush out of here
呃冲出这里
I can't wait to see what I see and show
我迫不及待地想看看我所看到的并向你展示
you along the way
[Music]
[音乐]
foreign
外国
[Music]
[音乐]祝
merry Merry Christmas
to you
你圣诞快乐
good morning everyone I made it
大家早上好
over to the mainland it's the next
第二天早上我到达了大陆
morning
I'm just packing up my camera equipment
我刚刚收拾好我的相机设备
already some good signs see there's
已经有一些好兆头 看到
three big eagles up here
这里有三只大鹰
plenty of fields out here with mice and
外面有很多田野，有老鼠和鼹鼠，
moles
and the short-eared owls
短耳猫头鹰
are
正在
looking for food during the winter
寻找食物 在冬天的
months
几个月里，
it is cooled out
它变冷了，
it's not
Frosty at the moment I think it's warmed
现在还不冷，我想它
up a tiny bit
有点暖和了，
but I'm out in the marsh
但我在沼泽地里，
apparently this week is
显然这周是
king tide week so where the ocean
大潮周，所以海水
floods this whole area
淹没了整个地区
and high tide is in another hour
，涨潮了 再过一个小时，
I do have rubber boots I didn't bring
我确实有橡胶靴，但我没有带，
them I brought just my hikers they're
我只带了我的徒步旅行者，它们是
waterproof
防水的，
and I've got my 500 set up to my Nikon
我已经将我的 500 设置到我的尼康
z9
and I'm out
，我要出去
here to see the short-eared owls we've
看我们的短耳猫头鹰
seen two so far by we there was another
到目前为止，我们已经看过两个了，还有另一个
buddy that was here he had to go to work
朋友在这儿，他必须去上班，和
it's great chatting with him
他聊天
nice always to have like two set of eyes
很棒，总是有两只眼睛，
and you could stand next to one another
你们可以并排站立，
and you can photograph
可以拍照，
but the two short-eared owls were way
但是这两个人很短 -有耳的猫头鹰
out there in some of the tall Reeds and
在一些高大的芦苇丛、
grass and Cocktails and they flew all
草丛和鸡尾酒丛中飞来飞去，它们
the way along kind of the shoreline up
沿着海岸线一路飞来飞去，
this way
so we were able to kind of pan with it
这样我们就可以用它来平底锅，其中
and one of them went over this way the
一只猫头鹰从这边飞过
other one went back over this way
另一个从这条路上回去
thing to look out for I guess if you're
要注意的事情我想如果你
out trying to photograph short-eared
想拍短耳
owls is that uh they have a shorter tail
猫头鹰是因为它们的尾巴较短
so there's a lot of Harrier Hawks
所以有很多鹞鹰
there's like
这里有大约
30 or 40 Harrier Hawks out here and they
30 或 40 只鹞鹰 它们
got a long tail and they flap quite a
有一条长尾巴，它们拍打得相当
bit so the short-eared owls are easy to
厉害，所以很容易发现短耳猫头鹰，
spot because they have such a shorter
因为它们的尾巴很短，
tail and they are a little bit slower
而且
with their uh their wingspan
它们的翼展有点慢，
so my
所以我的
shutter speed is at 1 1600 I might go up
快门速度是 1 1600 I 可能会上升到
to 2000 or 25 100 to capture some of
2000 或 25 100 以捕捉
their in-flight movements so I make sure
他们的一些飞行中的动作，所以我确保
that I have nice tack Sharp Images
我有很好的粘性 Sharp Images
and I'm photographing it f 6.3 my ISO
并且我正在拍摄它 f 6.3 我
right now is 1600.
现在的 ISO 是 1600。
is it actually what is my ISO yeah ISO
这实际上是我的 ISO 是的 ISO
is 1600
是 1600
wow so the Ravens are chasing the
哇所以乌鸦正在追逐
short-eared owls kind of harassing them
短耳猫头鹰有点骚扰他们
there are so many like moles and mice
有很多像鼹鼠和老鼠
like even right where I am right now
甚至就在我现在所在的地方
uh you can hear them in the field
呃你可以听到他们在田野里
squeaking and moving moving around
吱吱作响并四处走动
some of the walls are huge
墙壁很大，
yeah the tide must have come up and
是的，一定是涨潮了，
so that's a good sign that there's
所以这是一个好兆头，表明有
plenty of food
很多食物
I've got uh some some bars some food
actually in my bag here
and I just gotta watch it because they
will try and get into my bag or
我的包或者
just don't want them chewing through it
只是不想让他们咀嚼它
or something crazy like that
或者像那个男人那样疯狂的东西
man it's chilly out
它很冷
but it's exciting because uh there are a
但是很令人兴奋因为呃有
few short-eared owls they are active
几只短耳猫头鹰它们
there's so many mice out here that the
很活跃这里有很多老鼠
worry is that they just you know fill up
担心他们只是 你知道用
on on the mice on the food and then
食物填满老鼠然后就是
that's it they're not active at all and
这样他们根本不活跃
you can be out here all day
你可以整天呆在这里
but I think with the harassment from the
但我认为受到
other Harrier Hawks
其他Harrier Hawks
Ravens and other birds
Ravens和其他鸟类的骚扰
it's keeping them a little bit active
它让他们有点 有点活跃，
so there's a lot of chases and stuff in
所以天空中有很多追逐和东西，
the sky really fun to photograph
拍摄起来真的很有趣，嗯，
um hard to record at times moving around
有时很难记录，
so much
if uh they're nice and low to the area
如果它们很好，并且离该地区很低，那么
it's you get this really beautiful kind
你就会得到这种非常美丽的
of landscape shot
风景
[Music]
[音乐 ]
[Laughter]
[笑声]
foreign
外国
[Music]
[音乐]
Ed out and kind of hiding myself
埃德出去，有点把自己藏
here in this tall brush
在这个高大的灌木丛中，
one so that the wildlife the birds
这样野生动物，
flying over and stuff don't really get
飞过的鸟儿和其他东西就不会真的
too startled or spooked by me I kind of
被我吓到或吓坏了我有点
blend in
融入
uh but two uh just because there's other
呃但是两个 呃，只是因为还有其他
birders and hikers and that sort of
观鸟者和徒步旅行者之类的
thing and I don't really want to be in
东西，我真的不想出现在
their shot and be noticed so the camo
他们的镜头中并被注意到，所以迷彩
actually is more for humans than it is
实际上更适合人类而不是
for wildlife because let's face it they
野生动物，因为让我们面对现实吧，他们
know I'm here they could probably smell
知道我是 在这里，他们可能会闻到我的味道，他们
me they could see me from I think Eagles
可以从那里看到我，我想老鹰队
is like two miles away like
就在两英里外，就像
yeah it's pretty pretty crazy
是的，这是非常疯狂的
foreign
外国音乐
[Music]
[音乐]，到目前为止
and I've counted so far I think five
我已经数过了，我想有五只
short eared owls
短耳猫头鹰，
it's it's hard to tell because
这很难说，因为
one will land and another one will take
有一只会 着陆，另一个会起飞，
off
so there's two or three out this way and
所以有两三个从这边出来，
one or two over here
一两个在这边，
it's just incredible watching them hunt
看着他们猎杀
all the
all the hairier Hawks
所有毛茸茸的老鹰，
have uh
kind of disappeared there is one that
呃，有点消失了，
I've seen but
我见过一个，但
over the last three hours there hasn't
在过去 三个小时 没有
been a whole lot of activity there's
太多的活动
some herons that are still plucking
一些苍鹭仍在
picking away at some uh fish and a few
采摘一些鱼和
other things
其他一些东西，仅此而已 然后
and that's it and then it was quiet for
安静了
two hours just sitting here freezing and
两个小时 只是静静地坐在这里
all of a sudden
突然间
one owl another owl they're all flying
一只猫头鹰另一只猫头鹰他们都在飞来飞去
around some of them are chasing one
其中一些正在互相追逐
another it's just been unreal I shot for
这只是不真实我拍摄了
probably 30 minutes Non-Stop
大约 30 分钟不停地
from video back to
从视频回到
taking stills
拍摄静止图像
I will say with the Nikon z9
我会说尼康 z9
um I haven't tried the A1 or the uh the
嗯我还没有尝试过 A1 或
Canon R5 but
佳能 R5，但
the autofocus is better with the
firmware up update I'm at the 3.0
固件更新后自动对焦更好 我在 3.0
firmware update
固件更新，
but it still hunts if the the subject
但它仍然会寻找在
which in this case is the owl
这种情况下是猫头鹰的主题
isn't like
是否
clearly visible for the camera to notice
清晰可见相机 注意
and to hold on to it so
并坚持下去，所以
um I feel like Sony
我觉得索尼
and Canon have come so far with their
和佳能的自动对焦已经走了这么远，
autofocus that I just hope Nikon can can
我只希望尼康可以
put up some new out updates
提供一些新的更新，
um but yeah so stoked to be out here
嗯，但是是的，很高兴来到这里，
I'm glad I went with the uh the fluid
我很高兴我去了 有了液压
head
头，
so that I can pan and move and and uh
这样我就可以平移和移动，
and get some great video with any
并且可以拍摄一些很棒的视频，
jerking moving around
I'm photographing now at like
我现在正在以大约
3200 of a shutter speed
3200 的快门速度拍摄
I was at 2000 but the owls kept on
我在 2000 时的快门速度，但猫头鹰不断
getting closer and closer and when I'm
靠近并且 更近了，当我
moving back and forth and and panning
来回移动并
with them I just thought there was just
与它们一起摇摄时，我只是觉得
too much blur
模糊太多了，
too much motion that was happening not
发生了太多运动，
just the owls that's moving I'm moving
不仅仅是猫头鹰在移动，我在移动，
there's some shaking because I'm excited
还有一些震动，因为我很兴奋
[Music]
[音乐 ]
foreign
外国
[Music]
[音乐]
here are some of the tips that I've
这是我
learned while being out photographing
在外出拍摄
the short-eared owls once I saw that
短耳猫头鹰时学到的一些技巧，一旦我看到该
there were short-aired owls in the area
地区有短耳猫头鹰
flying around I picked a location that
飞来飞去，我就选择了
had the best backdrop composition
背景构图最好的位置
foreground elements and I just hunkered
前景元素，我只是蹲下
down there's no sense in picking up and
来，没有意义去捡起和
moving to where the owls are flying to
移动到猫头鹰飞来飞去的地方，
and from because the the space isn't
因为空间不是
that large and they're going to come
那么大，它们会
back fly around
回来飞来飞去，
there is also more than one short-eared
还有不止一个短片 -early
owl so your chances of waiting and
owl 所以你等待并
seeing one fly by you is at a higher
看到一只飞过你的机会更高
rate
and I noticed other photographers kind
，我注意到其他摄影师
of walking to and from and towards the
有点来回走近
short-eared owls they would see them fly
短耳猫头鹰，他们会看到它们飞回
back towards me so I'd see them hike all
我身边，所以我会看到 他们一路徒步
the way back towards me it didn't make
回到我这没有
any sense especially if you're carrying
任何意义，特别是如果你
around a tripod and all your heavy gear
带着三脚架和所有沉重的装备
pick the best composition best backdrop
选择最好的构图最好的背景
best foreground and just wait so for me
最好的前景然后等待我
I don't want to keep moving around
我不想保留 四处走动，
because the background kind of changes
因为背景有点改变了
the height of the grass there's that
草的高度，
popcorn kind of flowers that I wanted to
我想
get in the foreground and some of the
在前景中得到那种爆米花花，还有一些
images with the short-eared owls as they
短耳猫头鹰狩猎时的图像，
hunt so that was very important for me
所以这对我来说非常重要
is the environment shots
是 环境拍摄
I find the best settings for owl
我发现猫头鹰摄影的最佳设置
photography is first and foremost your
首先是你的
shutter speed seems to be king to be
快门速度似乎是
able to capture the birds in flight now
能够捕捉飞行中的鸟类的王者现在
the shorter owls can move quite fast
较短的猫头鹰可以移动得非常快，
especially when they're chasing one
特别是当他们互相追逐
another or they're being chased and so
或他们正在 被追赶，所以
I've I found that when they're far away
我发现当他们离得很远时，
about 1600 of a second was a great
大约 1600 秒是一个很好的
shutter speed I'm sure you can go slower
快门速度
than that but since I'm moving there's
there's the tripod and and there could
be shaking from wind they're moving I I
被风吹得摇摇欲坠，我
figured 1600 was was slow as I wanted to
想 1600 很慢，因为我
go and then if there were mid-range 2000
想去，然后如果有 2000 的中档
and then closer then it's 2500 so I
，然后更接近 2500，所以我
would just roll the shutter and go ahead
会卷起快门继续前进，
and hope that I got some shots now I was
希望我能得到一些 shots now 我在
out there for the whole day so I could
外面呆了一整天，所以我可以
actually check to see if things were in
实际检查一下
focus so that was good
um you know next would be my f-stop so I
was shooting with an F4 lens and I try
not to shoot It Wide Open one for it
是否聚焦 它是全开的，因为它的
being such a shallow depth of field
景深很浅，
afraid of missing kind of focus but also
害怕错过某种焦点，但也
uh it's a little bit softer I think on
呃，它有点柔和，我认为在
the extremes and shooting wide openness
极端情况下，开阔的镜头更
a little softer so I didn't go any any
柔和一点，所以我没有
wider than 4.5
比 4.5 更宽
I think the highest in my my sweet spot
我认为我最喜欢的最高点
would be F 6.3 but sometimes you just
是 F 6.3，但有时你只是
don't get the light that you need and
得不到你需要的光然后
then my ISO I had it on auto ISO so
我的 ISO 我把它放在自动 ISO 上所以
shutter was locked in my aperture I
快门被锁定在我的光圈里我
moved here and there at times depending
有时会在这里和那里移动
on the lighting and then my ISO kind of
取决于光线，然后我的 ISO
just filled in the blank
有点填补了空白，
so that's my camera settings
所以这就是我的相机设置，
um a big thing was a tripod I was blown
嗯，一个重要的东西是三脚架，我
away by by people that other
被那些
photographers that came down with camera
带着
equipment that they're hand holding now
他们现在手持的相机设备下来的摄影师震惊了
I have a 200 500 here and my camera body
我这里有一个 200 500 和我的相机机身
and and so I could hand hold that for a
，所以我可以用手握住它
bit but I feel like you're you're adding
一会儿，但我觉得如果你要整天拍摄三脚架，你会增加
to
movement and strain on the shoulders if
运动和肩膀的压力
you're going to be shooting all day
tripod is like a must so if you like
就像必须的，所以如果你喜欢
this content and you want to see more of
这个内容并且你想看到更多，
it please subscribe give me the thumbs
请订阅给我竖起
up that always helps out and click that
大拇指，这总是有帮助的，
notification Bell if you want to see
如果你想看到
more videos like this
更多这样的视频，请单击该通知铃，
just hiking back I think I broke the mic
只是徒步回来我想我破产了
off of my camera
关闭我相机的麦克风 祝
merry Merry Christmas
to you all right we need to put on some
你圣诞快乐 好吧，我们需要播放一些
Christmas music so you don't listen to
圣诞音乐，这样你就不会听
me sing
我唱歌了